## Randall Bonilla, Software Developer/Teacher/Data Entry

83316420, randallgbc@gmail.com

LINKS	Upwork Freelance			
PROFILE	Passionate learner, looking to improve and teach if possible, a data lover (Data Entry, Data analyst) and a inveterate programmer, with expertise in Java, C++ and C#, Learning Java Script and Python.  Interested in working with people and making a work group as successful as possible with leadership and positivism.  I love technology, being self-taught since 2018, making my knowledge passion invest in myself, quick learner. The investments made include two internet connections, personal computer and a laptop to work remotely.			
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY				
Aug 2019 — Dec 2019	Head Coach, Mad Revolution Gaming			San Jose, Costa Rica
	Head coach and wellness coach for a esports organization, using pedagogical techniques and helping young people to improve at a game that can also mean the future career for some of them, we succeed at getting the third place and winning a promotion tournament to reach first division on the national esports scene.			
Jun 2021 — Sep 2021	Customer Service Agent, SYKES Costa Rica			Heredia, Costa Rica
	Customer service agent with high metrics from the beginning of the training and along the job, giving quick solutions and solving problems with ease, while connecting with the customer and making the customer service experience better with each interaction.			
Jun 2021 — Sep 2022	Head Coach, Valhalla Legion			Panama City
	Head Coach focused on the player development and psychological reinforcement for a team looking to hold a spot on the Central American and Caribbean League, applying daily sessions, doing weekly work plans and videos to reinforce the educational process of being an esports player.			
Oct 2022 — Nov 2022	Professor, Saint Peter's School			Curridabat
	<ul> <li>Continually offered a variety of teaching methods and curricular perspectives.</li> <li>Worked with diverse students and successfully contributed to the department's mission.</li> <li>Worked with a team to research and develop new learning material for students.</li> <li>Remained committed to helping each student grow and learn as an academic scholar.</li> <li>Evaluated student performances, assignments and classwork.</li> <li>Continually fostered the notion that all opinions and ideas matter.</li> </ul>			
EDUCATION				
Jul 2016 — Nov 2017	High School Bachelor, Valley Forge San Jose			
Feb 2019 — Present	Bachelor in System Engineering, Universidad Latina de Costa Rica Here			Heredia
SKILLS	Fast Learner	Expert	Microsoft Office	Experienced
	Adaptability	Expert	Creative Thinking	Experienced
	Teamwork	Expert	Problem Solving	Expert
LANGUAGES	Spanish; Castilian	Native speaker	English	Highly proficient
HOBBIES	Photography, Hackathons			

COURSES

Oct 2022 — Nov 2022

Google IT Support Professional Certificate, Google